jonathan p. healy

jonathan.p.healy@gmail.com | 858.395.4047

Full Stack Web Developer with a B.A. in Business Administration. Experienced in management within the service industry. Bold curiosity in learning new technologies and excited for the challenges that lay ahead. Strengths in HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, MySql, JavaScript, JQuery, and NodeJS.

EDUCATION

University of California San Diego

Full Stack Web Development Program

2017

- An intensive 12-week long course dedicated to designing and full stack web development
- Skills learned consisted of HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars JS, & React Js

University of California Riverside

B.S. Business Administration

2009

- Accolades
 - Brotherhood chairman of Kappa Alpha Order and member of Interfraternity Council
 - Nicodemus Wilderness Project Award, issued for participation in environmental cleanup tasks on behalf of the University

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Foupon 2017

- A restaurant web application that allows you to "like" or "dislike" nearby eaterys and will in turn populate your profile with applicable coupons to your favorite spots!
- Contributing backend developer in a team of four
- JavaScript, JQuery, Google Places API, Sqoot API
- https://github.com/frogman91/Foupon

LIRI 2017

- Command line node app to return tweets, song information, or movie information
- App logs commands
- Node.js, NPM Packages: Request, Spotify, Twitter
- https://github.com/jheal006/liri-node-app

Bamazon 2017

- Command line interface which mimics a storefront application
- Node.js, NPM Packages: Request, MySql
- https://github.com/jheal006/bamazon

jonathan p. healy

jonathan.p.healy@gmail.com | 858.395.4047

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sunset Motors, Inc. San Diego, CA

07/2013 - 05/2017

Operations Manager

- In charge of day to day operations including customer service, long term reservation booking, and fleet maintenance of over 100 vehicles.
- Pricing and rate control across multiple brands

Drivetime, Inc. Riverside, CA

07/2011 - 06/2013

Sales Associate/Underwriter

- Verified customer credit ratings, worthiness, and analyzed credit reports as a basis for loan options and terms.
- Customer service specialist and sales liaison between senior loan underwriters, management and the customer base

Sunset Motors, Inc. San Diego, CA Rental Agent

02/2010 - 06/2011